So friends, ICICI Bank has disclosed its Quarter 4
numbers.  So let's
see what the data is inside the numbers for Quarter 4,
in the cross here.  So, if we
talk about the last quarter,
in the last quarter the company had
generated a total income of Rs 4934 crore.  Last
year it was Rs 49690
crore, whereas now if you look at it, you can see the total income of the company
going up to Rs 50584 crore.
So if we go year after year, you are seeing a jump of
around 2% in the total income of the company every year.
Whereas if we
go on quarterly basis, then on quarterly
basis also there is a rise of around 2 to 2.5%.
So look at the total income of the company,
you will see it increasing both year to year and quarter to quarter.  It has
not increased much
but it is seen increasing.
Talking about interest income, see,
in the last quarter it was Rs 41,965 crore, last
year it was Rs 42,430 crore, whereas if you look at it now,
you are seeing Rs 43,275 crore.  So if we
look at it here also, you are seeing a jump of around 2% year on year
while on quarterly basis
you are seeing a jump of around 3%.  So
you are seeing the company's revenue increasing.  In
such a situation, let us see what the net interest income of the company is.  That means let's see
what NIs turn out to be.
So last year the
net interest income of the company was Rs 21193
crore.  Talking about the last quarter, the
company's net interest income in the last quarter was Rs
crore.  Whereas if you look at it now, the
net interest income of the company in this quarter is
seen increasing to Rs 22979 crore.   If we
look here, you can see
a significant jump in the net interest income of the company
because if we
go on a quarterly basis, there is a jump of around 5%.
Whereas as the years go by,
you are seeing a growth of around 8 to 9%.
So you are seeing good net interest income of the company.
However, I have reports from some multiple brokerage
houses.  It must have come before you.
If you look at that, then
mostly it was also believed that the
NI of the company in this quarter can be seen coming
between Rs 22700 crore to Rs 22900 crore.
So you
can say that
you are seeing something around or slightly better than what the market had anticipated.
So
you are getting good net interest income.
Talking about expenses, it was Rs
31,978 crore in the last quarter and Rs 326 crore last year,
whereas if we look at it now, the company's expenses are Rs
32,385 crore.  So let's
look at the expenses as well.  So anyway, you are seeing it under the control of the company to a great extent.
Let us see what the company's provision is.
So see, in the last quarter the
company had lost ₹555 crore in the form of provisions.
Last year it was 890 crores, now it is only
around 96 crores.  So
you will see a big decline in provisions
both year-on-year and quarter-on-quarter.
So looking at the provision, it looked
very wonderful.  Because let me
tell you that you are seeing a provision of Rs 96 crore.
Whereas the market
estimate was between Rs 1100 to 1600 crores.
So you are seeing very few provisions.
Let us see what the profit of the company
turns out to be.  So see,
in the last quarter the company had a profit of Rs 11317 crore.
Last year it was Rs 12629 crore, whereas if you
look at it now, you can see it increasing to Rs 13701 crore.
So if we look at the company's
profits, you saw a huge increase.  There
is a jump of around 8% in the company's profits.  Whereas if we
go on quarterly basis, then here
you are seeing an even bigger jump.  There
is a jump of around 22% in the company's profit on a
quarterly basis, due to
reduction in provisions, you have seen a big jump.
However, how much has the company
done this?  Multiple reports around Rs 13,701 crore must have
come before you.
If you look at it, then most of the brokers
believed that the profit of the company can be
seen to remain within Rs 13,000 crore.  The
average estimate from maximum to maximum comes out to be around Rs 13,200 crore.
But let's see here it is 13,700
crores.  So you can say that if you
look at both revenue and profit, you are seeing better results in this quarter.
Talking about EPS, it was ₹15.84 in the last quarter and
₹17.87 last year, and if you look at it now,
you can see it increasing to ₹19.15.
And in such a situation, let us see what the NPA of the company
turns out to be.  So look,
gross in pay last year was 1.667%.  If you
look now, it has fallen to 1.40.  Whereas
in the last quarter it was around 1.53, whereas if we
look at the net NPA, it was 0.39% last year.
Right now it is 0.33, whereas
in the last quarter it was around 0.37, so if you look at the net NPA,
gross and pay, you have seen both falling.
Whereas the market had estimated
that it might be around 0.38.
So you have got to see that better too.
So you can say that if you look at every sharp
scale, you will see better numbers of the company.
Profits are good.  Revenues are good.   The
company's provisions are very low and the company's
NPAs are also good.  So the
company's numbers are looking better from all angles.  Let's
see
how the market reacts to this.  If you like the video, please like it.
Also, please subscribe to the channel.